Everybody has been wondering is AMD going to bring more than eight cores to the third Gen Ryzen desktop processor family.
每个人都想知道AMD是否会推出8核以上的3代锐龙CPU产品线
And today I'm very happy to say the answer is absolutely yes.
今天我很高兴地宣布：毫无疑问!
Good moring,Taipei!
你好，台北！
This morning, we're going to talk about a lot of different things.
今早，我们将会谈论非常多的不同的事情
We're going to give you a brief update on where we are with our data center products,
我们将会对我们的数据中心产品做一个简要介绍
the second generation Rome.
这就是二代Rome
We're going to talk a bit about Navi and then third Generation AMD Ryzen CPUs.
我们将会讨论一些关于Navi的事情，接下来就是3代AMD Ryzen CPU。
So with that let me bring you to our first announcement of the morning.
了解这些后，让我来向大家介绍早上的第一个发布项目
You saw what we could do in supercomputing capabilities,
我们在超级计算方面的能力众所皆知,
and what we announcing today with Microsoft is we are bringing that supercomputing capability of scale into the azure cloud.
我们今天和微软一起将这种能力赋予Azure cloud.
and the idea here is that we have the ability to have the largest cluster of EPYC CPUs over ten thousand CPUs
我们有能力构建最大的EPYC CPU集群，超过10000个CPU
that will really allow you to simulate very, very large tasks.
这将允许你模拟非常非常庞大的任务
and our first customer has already said that
第一家客户已经反映
they have been able to get over seven thousand five hundred times speed up by using the azure cloud with EPYC compared to what they could do before.
在azure cloud上使用EPYC，可以做到比之前的系统快7500倍。
I also want to give you an update on our second generation EPYC processor Rome.
我还要介绍一下我们的二代EPYC CPU: Rome
It's built on seven nanometer technology.
使用7纳米制程，
It's up to sixty four Zen two cores.
使用第二代Zen架构，最多64核心
It has incredible compute and I/O and bandwidth capability.
它有不可思议的计算能力、I/O性能和带宽
because of the way we architected this device
这都源于我们的架构设计
in our labs and in our customer's labs is we see up to twice the performance,
在我们和客户的实验室里，都能获得最高翻倍的性能增长
2x performance per socket compared to our previous generation.
每个插槽的性能都两倍于我们前代的产品
And on floating point workloads, we see up to 4X.
而浮点性能更是高达4倍
You really need to build a GPU architecture that goes across PCs,consoles and the cloud,
你真的需要构建一个跨多平台的GPU架构
and that's exactly what we set out to do.
这正是我们着手在做的
So Navi is our new family of Radeon GPUs.
因此，Navi成了Radeon GPU的一个新产品线
Just last month.
就在上个月
Sony announced the first application of Navi
索尼宣布了Navi的首次应用
They announced that their next generation Playstation is going to be powered by AMD
下一代PlayStation将会使用AMD产品
with our semi custom portfolio using Navi as well as our Zen 2 products.
使用我们的半定制Navi方案和二代Zen CPU
What I talk about Navi,
当我在谈论Navi时，
I also talk about Navi as it relates to our PC products,
我也在讨论Navi和我们的PC产品的关系
Navi has an all new seven nanometer RDNA architecture.
Navi 有全新的7纳米工艺和RDNA(Radeon DNA)架构
When you look at the architectural improvements of RDNA  in our first generation
当你回顾我们第一代RDNA产品的架构改进
compared to our Vega gaming generation,
和我们的Vega游戏系列相比,
what we see is 1.25X performance per clock,
我们看到的是每时钟1.25倍的性能
and then when you put that together,
然后你把这些因素放在一起
both the architecture, The design capability, as well as the process technology.
综合架构、设计能力和处理技术
we're seeing one 1.5X or higher performance per watt capability on the New Navi Products as a result of our RDNA.
在我们RDNA架构的Navi产品上，可以得到1.5倍甚至更高的每瓦性能
So let me introduce you to the first Navi GPU.
因此，请让我介绍第一款Navi GPU
You'll see that on average,
总体上看,
the RX 5700 GPU beats our competition by roughly 10% performance in this very early edition of the game demo.
在这个游戏demo的早期版本中，RX5700比老黄的2070性能高出大约10%
so I'm Super excited about that.
我对此非常激动
So we will be launching everywhere in the world at retail and details are available in July.
7月份全球上市，具体细节也会一并提供
Are you guys ready?
各位准备好了吗
The core truly is the engine of our third gen Ryzen,
最重要的是3代Ryzen的引擎,
and Zen2 is an incredible core.
Zen2是一个非同凡响的核心架构.
and so today I'm happy to share with you that
因此，今天我很高兴能和大家分享
Zen 2, In the PC workloads actually achieves 15% IPC uplift.
Zen 2在个人电脑负载环境下达成了15% IPC(Instruction Per Clock)提升.
so let's start with the very first third Gen Ryzen product,
让我们从第一款3代锐龙产品开始吧
the 3700X is the world's first seven Nanometer desktop CPU.
3700X是世界第一款7纳米桌面级CPU.
It has 8 cores 16 threads 4.4 gigahertz boost frequency,
8核16线程，4.4GHz动态加速频率,
36MB of total cache and all in an amazing 65 watts of TDP.
36MB缓存(4MB L2和32MB L3)，这一切仅需65瓦TDP.
the second gen Ryzen is a great set of products,
2代锐龙有一系列产品,
but what we're seeing with the 3700X is significant double digit performance
但我们可以看到3700X有着的两位数性能增长幅度，
in both single threaded and multi threaded workloads at that significantly lower power.
同时体现在单线程和多线程的性能中，并且功耗很低
And as we turn through this realistic ray-traced scene,
通过这个逼真的光线追踪场景,
you may notice that the Ryzen 3700X is quite a bit faster.
你会发现3700X快了非常多
In fact, it's about 1/3 faster than the competing part.
事实上，这比牙膏厂快了差不多三分之一
So let me introduce you to the next member of the Ryzen7 family,
接下来介绍Ryzen7的另一位成员,
the Ryzen7 3800X.
Ryzen7 3800X.
The boost clock goes up to four point five gigahertz,
加速频率提升至4.5GHz,
36MB of total cache, and you see this is now at 105watts.
36MB缓存(4MB L2和32MB L3)，TDP仅为105W.
So take a look at the improvements and you can see tremendous double digit performance improvement
了解这些改进后，你会发现惊人的两位数性能提升
because we really believe gaming performance is critical and we designed the 3800X for gaming performance,
因为我们坚信游戏性能极其重要，而且3800X就是为了游戏性能设计
both of them eight cores, sixteen threads
它们都是8核16线程,
and the great thing about it is this beautiful PUBG demo that we built and recorded to reliably test the performance of this game.
这个吃鸡演示的一大好处是我们可以构建、记录和测试游戏的性能
And what you'll see is that both processors are about the same.
你可以看到两个处理器效果差不多.
and in fact that's ideal.
事实上，这很理想化.
I know as a gamer that I want a processor that gives so much performance to the GPU that it's out of the way.
我知道作为一个玩家，需要一个高性能且不会拖GPU后腿的处理器
I don't even have to worry about the fact that my GPU is being bottleneck by the processor.
我不需要担心CPU成为性能瓶颈
So what we want to show you next Roberts going to help me.
接下来展示的内容需要Roberts的帮助.
We're going to show you the 3800 X with The Navi Radeon rx 5700 series with X 570 Mother Board
我们将要展示 3800X和Navi Radeon rx 5700系列以及 X570主板
and with a tremendous amount of i/o capability using PCI Express Gen 4.
和4代PCI-E提供的惊人I/O性能.
So this is actually the world's first PCI Express Gen 4 ready gaming PC.
事实上这是世界上第一款4代PCI-E的游戏PC.
We built two systems on your left,a PCI Gen 3 system and on your right exclusively and uniquely from AMD, a PCI Express Gen 4 system.
我们搭建了两台系统，左边的是3代PCI系统，右边是AMD独有的4代PCI-E系统
And this is running the upcoming 3Dmark PCI Express feature test,
正在跑的是即将发布的3Dmark PCI Express特性测试
which has designed to answer the question
这个测试用于展示
How much extra graphics performance can you get from PCI Gen 4 versus Gen 3
对比3代，你可以从4代PCI-E中得到多少额外性能
and the answer is clear.
结果很清楚
in its large, up to 69% more performance for graphics from having PCI Gen 4 .
有4代PCI技术的电脑，图形性能高出了将近69%.
AMD is pushing gaming beyond eight cores.
AMD不止于8核.
and today I am so proud to introduce the new AMD Ryzen9 family.
今天我将满怀自豪地展示全新的AMD Ryzen9家族.
Take a look at AMD Ryzen9.
看看AMD Ryzen9.
It's this beautiful or what.
它就是这么漂亮.
the Ryzen9 3900X is the absolutely first mainstream desktop processor,
Ryzen9 3900X是完全意义上第一款主流桌面级处理器,
with 12 cores and 24threads.
拥有12核心24线程
We have four point six gigahertz boost seventy megabytes of total cash,
4.6Ghz加速频率，70MB缓存(6MB L2和64MB L3),
and it's all in one hundred and five watts.
这一切仅需105瓦功耗.
This is a $1200 processor on the left versus the AMD Ryzen9 3900X on your right
左边的是1200刀的牙膏厂CPU，右边是3900X
and what you see from every box is a processing thread.
你看到的每个小方框都是一个处理线程.
and as we come to the finish, the difference is clear.
当我们跑完测试，区别就很明显了.
We finished in about 32 seconds versus the competitors, 38 seconds.
我们用了32秒，而对手用了38秒
And that's about an 18 percent performance improvement for AMD.
AMD有18%的性能优势.
and we're going core to core, twelve versus twelve,
我们单核心对单核心，12核对12核
which means Zen2 , is simply faster.
这意味着Zen2显然更快
Third Gen Ryzen is amazing, when you look at the 3700X,
3代Ryzen非常amazing，当你看到3700X的规格时,
what we believe is the price point for an entry level 8 core device should be 329$.
我们认为入门级8核处理器的价格应该是2269￥.
and when you move up to the 3800X again,
再往上的是3800X,
we want as many people to have this as possible.
我们想让尽可能多的人拥有它
So this will retail for 399$.
因此零售价将会是2752￥
最后
and finally,
the Ryzen9 family.
Ryzen9系列
We love this guy because we love that we can bring something to the market that nobody has ever done before
我们非常喜欢Ryzen9，因为我们热爱将从来没有人做过的产品投入市场
we compared against our competition, whose device is more than 1100$.
对比竞品，那些超过1100$的CPU(i9 9920x淘宝售价过万)
But we believe that we want as many people as possible to have the Ryzen9 3900X.
我们想要让尽可能更多的人拥有Ryzen9 3900X.
So when this goes on sale,
因此当它发售时，
it will retail for 499$ !
价格将是3442￥!!!!(牙膏厂出来挨打！)
It's half the price.
一半的价格！
that's half the price of our competition.
这是友商一半的价格！(指i9 9920X)
with much much more performance.
而且性能不知道高到哪里去了.
I am very, very proud to tell you
我非常非常自豪地告诉大家，
that all of these processors go on shelf on July 7th.
所有这些处理器将在7月7日上市！
双语字幕：PolestarX             AMD YES!